Le-Var Johnson
Hartford, CT 06105
levar1982@yahoo.com
paragon860@gmail.com
1-917-204-8614
 
Professional Summary 
 
Particularly focused on marketing, promotion and sales strategies in business. Entrepreneurial spirit with track record of innovation and increase sales. Demonstrated ability to deliver local market strategies to enhance customer loyalty and engagement. Communicates and motivate colleagues to accomplish business outcomes. Solid ability in conducting and analyzing research to further business objectives. Team player that enjoys leadership positions to find creative and innovative ways to solve problems, while being self-motivated and on -task. Ability to manage and accomplish multiple projects within time assigned. Ongoing creative ability in facilitating social media sites and website design to advance promotion and marketing. Strong written, oral and presentation skills. Actively enjoys working both nationally and internationally to enhance and create marketing, sales and promotional campaigns, while working with compliance, legal departments and budgets to stimulate customer interest in a particular business. Always delivers upon the brands promise. Superior customer service by ensuring customer care to all customers. Skilled in using common computer programs and also worked with statistical analysis programs. Enjoys working with people of diverse backgrounds and is open to travel.


 
Education
Middle-town Adult Education 
Diploma 
Manchester Community College 
Business Administration Entrepreneurship 
GPA - 3.0, Current Graduation date December 2012
     
  

            Trainings/ Certificates and Volunteer Work
Mixed Martial Arts
Public Service License
Certificates
CPR/First AID/ AED
 
  
                    
                      Pop Warner Midget Football League
                      Asst. Coach for Pop Warner high school aged football team
                      Weaver High School Football team
                       Asst. Varsity Coach
                      Coordinate fundraisers and team promotion
                      Kept statistics 
                      Facilitate offensive and defensive drills
                     Organizes player nutrition plans 
  
         Paragon Talent International, LLC
     
         SPM strategist (Sales, Promotions, Marketing) 
         Paragon SPM is a Small Business strategist for start- up companies in the Connecticut area.
         Creates Swot analysis, marketing analysis, and plans for businesses
            Event coordinator 
            Promotion creations 
            Marketing Startegist
 
Employment
 
Premier Limousine – Current
Berlin, CT 
Sharp driver
            Chauffeur around Northeast 
Customer Service
Travel Concierge 
             Gold Club 
Hartford, CT 
Security and Promotions 
Promotions & Marketing
Checked identification 
Host bachelor parties, birthday parties
Host graduation parties
Cashier
Remove obnoxious customers quick, quiet, and efficiently 
Non- Violent Intervention
 
　Rent a Center  
Hartford, CT 
Customer Account Representative 
Served customers by providing product and service information 
Resolve product service problems. 
Highest sales in the district for store 3961 in the first quarter for 2008
1 year Certificate of Achievement Award
 
·         Take weekly payments from new and existing customers
·         attract potential customers by answering product service questions
·         suggesting information about other products and services
·         opening customer accounts by recording account information
·         maintain customer records by updating account information
·         resolve product or service problems by clarifying the customer’s complaint
·         determining the cause of the problem selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem
·         expediting correction or adjustments
·         following up to ensure resolution
·         maintain financial accounts by processing customer adjustments
·         recommend potential products or service to management by collecting customer information and analyzing customer needs 
 
 
 
References
 
General Manager for the Gold Club
Mike Wright 
1-203-671-2321
 
Admissions Rep for John Casablanca
Salena Karjohn 
1-860-888-9470
 
 
 
 
 
 

