Wanda Sanchez
885 Belmont Avenue
Springfield, MA. 01108
(413)896-8203 ? wreilly09@comcast.net


OBJECTIVE

To obtain a position in an office environment utilizing my varied skills and abilities with the potential for growth and development. 

HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATIONS

 	Bilingual: English/Spanish (read, write and speak).
 	Combined skills as self-starter and team worker. 
 	Well-organized and welcome new challenges.
 	Self-motivated and confident in making independent decisions.
 	Type: 60 wpm

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS 

BUISNESS
	
 	 Acquired computer skills in keyboarding, Microsoft Word, Excel, Access and PowerPoint.
 	 Developed Internet skills by conducting on-line research and communicating via E-mail.
 	Trained in fundamental business principles including the DISC program to establish effective business strategies. 
 	Refined English grammar and business skills necessary in the office environment. 
 	Participated in Work Development Seminars. 

CUSTOMER SERVICE

 	Greeted customers and determined their specific needs. 
 	Handled customer issues with patience, sensitivity and tact. 
 	Provided fast and efficient, yet courteous service. 

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

      Ikon Office Solutions, Holyoke, MA			                     November 2008 - August 2009
      Mail/Print Customer Service 
 	Received and sorted out mail for Doctors.
 	Sent outgoing mail using a postal machine.
 	Created and printed out perscription pads and hospital forms using different printers (110's 105)
 	Used many different machines to make the forms(bindery, laminating, drilling, padding,etc).
 	Answered phones, sorted and distributed appointments as they came in.

     WANDA SANCHEZ - Page 2

     McDonalds, Chicopee, MA                                                                 October 2004 - September 2008
     Shift Manager

 	Trained co-workers in a positive and potential manner.
 	Ran the restaurant and ran the floor on my shift.
 	Gave employees their breaks and took care of any customer problems. 
 	Did the cash outs and deposits.
 	Fixed any problems in the restaurant.

      Tyco Healthcare, Chicopee, MA                                                              September 2003 - June 2004
      Packer/Inspector

 	Packaged and inspected medical supplies.
 	Trained co-workers in a positive and potential manner. 
 	Managed my own workstation. 
 	Accomplished deadlines and increased production.

      Association for Community Living, Springfield, MA                            October 2002 - January 2003
      Support Person One

 	Assisted disabled elderly patients with personal hygiene.
 	Aided elderly with feeding and nutrition.
 	Washed, dried, and folded laundry.
 	Prepared lunches and filled backpacks for next day's activities.

      Solutions For Staffing, Springfield, MA                                              March 2002 - September 2002
      Receptionist/Office Clerk

 	Performed daily office duties including, typing, filing, and customer service.
 	Utilized multi-telephone lines to meet the individual needs of clients. 
 	Entered data into computer efficiently.
 	Maintained files and kept accurate records.
 	Provided translation for Hispanic clients. 

      Taco Bell, Springfield, MA                                                                          October 1999 - July 2000
      Cashier

 	Reconciled cash drawer at beginning and end of shift.
 	Greeted customers and took food and drink orders.
 	Operated cash register.





WANDA SANCHEZ - Page 3

      Department Of Correction (Seasonal)                                                           June 1999 - August 1999
      Assistant Secretary

 	Performed data entry of daily transportation logs.
 	Handled all telephone, fax, and e-mail traffic.
 	Typed company correspondences, filed memos and letters.
 	Provided secretarial support to President's staff.


EDUCATION

      Jump Start Certificate Program,  Holyoke Community College, Holyoke MA              March 2005
     
     Completed the 540- hour Certificate Program of academic training in English/Business                            Communication, Customer Service, Computer Skills, Life and Job Skills, Applied Mathematics, Reading for Information and Locating Information.

      High School Diploma , Agawam High School, Agawam, MA                                              June 2000











